revcontent.com 2018-06-29

# Revcontent | Revcontent's Privacy Policy

[

](https://www.revcontent.com/)

### If you do not want Revcontent to use the information it collects for purposes of showing ads that are targeted to your interests, you may opt out by clicking the below “Opt-Out” button  
If you use multiple devices and/or multiple browsers, you must opt out on each device/browser (even if you login to Revcontent using social media credentials).  You also must opt out again if you clear your cookies, opt out again.

If you have opted out, a new page will open and you should see a message indicating that your opt out was successful.

**REVCONTENT PRIVACY POLICY**

 REVCONTENT PRIVACY POLICY

Last Updated & Effective Date: May 25, 2018

This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by Revcontent, LLC (“Revcontent”). 

Revcontent operates a network platform through which web properties can display certain third party content such as articles, videos, blog posts, and advertisements on their sites (the “Services”).  This Privacy Policy describes how Revcontent collects, uses, and discloses information when you visit this website (“the Site”) and websites and mobile applications that integrate the Services.  
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time.  If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy.  We encourage you to check back regularly to stay informed about our information practices and the choices available to you.

COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

_Information We Collect Automatically Through the Services_

In order to help provide recommendations and promoted content that is relevant to your interests, we automatically collect certain information when you access websites and mobile applications that incorporate the Services. This information reflects information about the websites you visit, the mobile applications you use, and how you interact with our Services. 

Browser and Device Information: We collect information about your browser and device, including your browser type, device type, IP address, user agent string, operating system, mobile carrier, and identifiers assigned to your browser or device.

Usage Data: We collect information about the websites and mobile applications you visit that integrate our Services and about the websites that you visit immediately prior to visiting a website that integrates our Services, including the date and time your browser or device accesses such websites and the specific pages accessed.

Click Data: We collect information about the content and ads that you click on within the Services.

_Information You Provide_

You may be able to customize your experience by logging in to Engage.IM through a social media service. If you do this, we will have access to certain information from that service, such as your name, profile information, likes, shares, posts, etc., in accordance with the authorization procedures determined by the social media service you use to 

login.

You also may be able to customize your Revcontent experience by registering as a user directly with the 

Revcontent and/or Engage.IM and selecting topics of interest to customize your experience. If you do this, we will have access to the information you provide in doing so, including your name, contact information, and any preferences or interests you select.

_Information We Collect from Other Sources_

We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Services.  For example, we may collect information about you from third parties, including our business partners, other advertising companies, and publicly available sources.

_Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies We Use to Collect Information_  
We use various technologies to collect information, including cookies, web beacons, web storage, unique device identifiers, and similar technologies.  Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us to tailor recommendations and promoted content to your preferences over time.  For example, we may use your web browsing information to show you specific recommendations and sponsored recommendations that we think will be of particular interest to you.  We may also collect information using web beacons (also known as "tracking pixels").  Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Services and help perform a variety of functions, including delivering cookies, counting visits, and understanding usage.  For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see "Your Choices" below.

USE OF INFORMATION

We use the information we collect to determine what content is most relevant to you, to disseminate recommendations and promoted content to you, and to understand,

measure, and report on how users interact with the Services.  We also use the information we collect from the Service to maintain and constantly improve upon the Services.

SHARING OF INFORMATION

We may share the information we collect as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy:

  * With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work or perform services on our behalf;
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, rule, regulation or legal process;
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property or safety of Revcontent or others;
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company;
  * Between and among Revcontent and any current or future parent, subsidiary and/or affiliated company; and
  * With your consent or at your direction.

We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.  For example, we may share de-identified information with advertisers that partner with us to help them understand how well their advertisements performed.

YOUR CHOICES

_Opting out of Personalized Content_

You may opt out of receiving personalized content and advertisements from Revcontent by clicking the “Opt Out” button at the top of this page.  When you opt out, we will set a cookie on your browser that tells us not to personalize recommendations or promoted content on that browser or to record information about the sites you are visiting.  If you use multiple devices and/or multiple browsers, you need to opt out on each device and browser you use, even if you login

to Revcontent using a social media account.

Please note that even after you have opted out, you will still see Revcontent recommendations and promoted content, but these recommendations and promoted content will not be personalized based on the sites you visit.

Note that if you clear your cookies, you will need to opt out again.

For information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for interest-based advertising purposes by companies that participate in the Digital Adverting Alliance, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices). If you are in the EU, you may opt out at the European Digital Advertising Alliance, [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).   

_Cookies_

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default.  If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies.  Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of some websites.

INFORMATION COLLECTED ON OUR WEBSITE

Advertisers and publishers may provide contact information through our Site to find out more about Revcontent, be contacted by a Revcontent representative, or 

to start working with Revcontent. Revcontent (and its agents and service providers) may use this information to respond to your request, to send you marketing communications, and for business purposes such as marketing and research. We will also use the information we collect from advertisers and publishers for invoicing and billing purposes. We will not rent or sell this information to other companies. You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from Revcontent by following the instructions in those emails or by emailing us at [privacy@revcontent.com](mailto:privacy@revcontent.com).  If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations. 

Revcontent may also work with third parties that collect data on our Site and on other websites to serve you targeted ads.  You can opt out of interest-based ads by companies that participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance opt out program by visiting about [http://optout.aboutads.info/](http://optout.aboutads.info/). If you are in the EU, you may opt out at the European Digital Advertising Alliance, [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

DATA RETENTION  
We store the information we collect for as long as is necessary for the purpose(s) for which we originally collected it. We may retain certain information for legitimate business purposes or as required by law.

DATA TRANSFERS AND PRIVACY SHIELD

Revcontent is based in the U.S.  As such, we and our service providers may transfer your information to, or store or access it in, jurisdictions that may not provide equivalent levels of data protection as your home jurisdiction.  We will take steps to ensure that your personal data receives an adequate level of protection in the jurisdictions in which we process it.

When we transfer personal data from the European Union or Switzerland to the United States, we comply with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss - U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States, respectively.

Revcontent has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.privacyshield.gov/](https://www.privacyshield.gov/).

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, we are committed to resolving complaints about our processing of your personal data. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our compliance with the Privacy Shield program should first contact us at [privacy@revcontent.com](mailto:privacy@revcontent.com)  We have further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to JAMS, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please contact or visit [https://www.jamsadr.com/file-an-eu-us-privacy-shield-or-safe-harbor-claim](https://www.jamsadr.com/file-an-eu-us-privacy-shield-or-safe-harbor-claim) for more information or to file a complaint. The services of JAMS are provided at no cost to you. Under certain conditions, you may be able to invoke binding arbitration to resolve your complaint. Revcontent is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission.

If we share personal data transferred to the U.S. under the Privacy Shield with a third-party service provider that processes such data on our behalf, then we will be liable for that third party’s processing in violation of the Privacy Shield Principles, unless we can prove that we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

HOW WE PROTECT THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
We take reasonable measures to help protect the information we collect from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration 

and destruction.  However, no transmission over the internet or electronic storage can be completely secure, so we cannot guarantee the absolute security of any data.

RESIDENTS OF THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (“EEA”), you have certain rights and protections under the law regarding the processing of your personal data.

_Legal Basis for Processing_

If you are a resident of the EEA, when we process your personal data we will only do so in the following situations:

  * We need to use your personal data to perform our responsibilities under our contract with you (e.g., processing payments for and providing the services you have requested).
  * We have a legitimate interest in processing your personal data. For example, we may process your personal data to provide content and advertisements that may be of interest to you, to communicate with you about changes to our Services, and to provide, secure, and improve our Services.
  * There is another applicable lawful basis under which we are permitted to process your personal data.

_Data Subject Requests_  
If you are a resident of the EEA, you have the right to access personal data we hold about you and to ask that your personal data be corrected, erased, or transferred.  You may also have the right to object to, or request that we restrict, certain processing.  If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us at [privacy@revcontent.com](mailto:privacy@revcontent.com)  

_Questions or Complaints_  
If you are a resident of the EEA and have a concern about our processing of personal data that we are not able to resolve, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the data privacy authority where you reside.  For contact details of your local Data Protection Authority, please see: [http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm).

CONTACT US

If you have any questions or need to contact us, please do so at [privacy@revcontent.com](mailto:privacy@revcontent.com) or at:

Revcontent UK Ltd  
Unit 4  
Riverside Court  
Lower Bristol Road   
Bath, Somerset, UK  
BA2 3DZ
